

# AMIR REZA ZARE

programmer



#### **OBJECTIVE**

I want to succeed in a stimulating and challenging environment, building the success of the company while I experience advancement opportunities.



# PERSONAL PROFILE

Mid Level Web Developer with +2 years of experience in programming. Experience in Mahya company with PHP, javascript language, and Laravel framework, QA platform in Paziresh24 company and Laravel Framework, Vue js in Glass company and Working with Artificial Intelligence at the University



# **EXPERIENCE**

# PROGRAMMER Ardakan Glass (10/2021 - present)

- programming with Laravel framework
- programming with Vue js
- Experience work with MySQL

### **DEVELOPER** paziresh24 (06/2021 - 10/2021)

- +500k downloaded in Google Play
- best app in health field in iran
- programming with Laravel framework
- Development with QA platform

# PROGRAMMER Mahya (08/2019 - 06/2021)

- programming with Cakephp framework
- programming with JavaScript,jQuery
- Cooperation with municipalities



## CERTIFICATES

- The SQL Programming Essentials 2021 Immersive Training Udemy
- <u>Python Django Full Social Media Course Python Django Full Social Media Course Udemy</u>
- Complete PYTHON Programming for Beginners
- Make Laravel and Laravel 8 APIs and Apps fast with blueprint-Udemy
- Learn Basic Data science and Python Libraries
- <u>Git & GitHub For Beginners Master Git and GitHub (2021)</u>
- Mastering Visual Studio Code



## **EDUCATION**

### **MEYBOD STATE UNIVERSITY**

bachelor of Computer Software Engineering(AI) 09/2018 - 2022



### **ACHIEVEMENTS**

**Member of university Scientific Association** 



## **SKILLS**

- Python
- Php
- Laravel
- Django
- Javascript
- jQuery
- html
- vue is
- Process Maker
- Cakephp
- MySQL
- Git
- opency
- tensorflow
- keras
- matplotlib
- pandas



## CONTACTS



+98 913 529 1501



Yazd, Iran (I'm Looking for Relocation Sponsor)



amirjoun2@gmail.com



linkedin.com/in/binahayat00